First, uh, let's get the update. Uh, how
is the accovery coming along? I saw
video that you're already running 18
miles per hour.
>> It's coming along pretty well. You know,
I'm four and a half months out of
surgery right now. You know, I'm just
kind of, you know, keep trying to keep
pushing, you know, and getting it
stronger so I can be prepared for this
upcoming season.
>> Good. Good. Now, what do you think of
your new home venue being Hard Rock
Stadium where you had a huge game uh
just last season with Louisville?
>> Man, it's crazy. Uh, I've been saying
that uh all all this uh this draft this
prejop stuff like what if I go to Miami?
What if I go to Miami? And it happened.
So, it's crazy. It's a blessing though.
It's God. God.
>> Cool. Appreciate it. Congratulations,
>> Chris.
>> Yep.
>> Hey, uh Chris Perkins from the South.
We got two Chrises here. How you doing?
>> I'm doing good. How are you?
>> I'm good. I'm good. Congratulations.
>> Thank you. Um, tell me about the injury
and whether it was deflating or whether
you just kind of took it in stride.
>> Uh, what do you mean by deflating?
>> Uh, did it were you discouraged? Did it
did it get you down? Were you, you know,
were you, I guess, frustrated or
depressed or angry or anything like
that?
>> Uh, it was frustrating at first when it
first happened, you know, cuz I never
had like a major injury like this. But,
you know, uh, I feel like, you know, God
put this in my uh this injury in my life
for a reason. I know it had me
frustrated last night just knowing that
I feel like I was better than you know
some of the guys that went off the board
but you know uh it was all you know guys
playing and you know I'm just blessed to
you know be in a good position no matter
it was first or second round you know
what I mean I'm I'm here and I'm you
know willing to give my all so I'm
ready. I've seen you play a few times
and you're a big receiver, physical,
good hands, um good speed, but you
describe your game to me and you tell me
what what you do well in in in your
opinion.
>> Uh I would say um I'm a allaround
receiver. Um a lot of people say they
was concerned by my route running, but
you know, if you go look at, you know,
me running routes here at Pro Days or
you know, some of my film, you know, I
run great routes. Uh uh I feel like I
do, you know, great with the ball in my
hands and run after catch. I'm a great,
you know, run out the kids player. I
feel like, you know, I'm physical. You
know, a lot of DBs can't deal with, you
know, a big guy like me. So, it's a lot
of things that I bring to the table.
>> All right. Thanks,
>> brother.
>> Joe.
>> Hey, Chris. It's Joe in Palm Beach.
Congratulations. Nice to meet you. Um, I
remember at the combine you mentioned a
couple of receivers that you like to
watch like uh Debo Samuel uh AJ Brown,
DK Medaf. Those guys all got pretty big
muscles.
>> H how are you able to leverage your
physical strength? How do you think that
helps you?
>> Uh I feel like, you know, it helped me a
lot in my game. Um I would say, uh how
do I leverage? I mean, I I work out, you
know, and just try to, you know, stay on
top of my, you know, my workout. So,
yeah.
>> What's your uh what what's the um
workout or exercise that you you think
you're most impressive at? Like, what do
your teammates go, man, that's pretty
good.
>> Uh I would say before I got here, I
would say my my uh back squatting. I was
pretty good at that, you know, and I
squatted, you know, a lot. Uh I don't
put no number on it, but you know, I was
good at uh power cleaning. I would say
uh invention too. Um I was just kind of
know doing you know Louisville you know
staff workout. So yeah.
>> All right. Congratulations.
>> Hey
>> Travis.
>> Hey Travis. Congratulations and welcome
to Miami. Man, I wanted to first start
by asking about the call and the moment
you found out you were going to the NFL.
Just talk about the emotions that you
felt last night when you got the call.
>> Man, it was it was so many emotions,
man. just just seeing, you know, me uh
drop down the board, it it hurt, but uh
I know um I play better with a chip on
my shoulder. So, you know, uh God did
that for a reason. And um you know, uh
it would happen, but um when I got that
phone call, it was it was it was a crazy
moment like you know, it it felt unreal.
Um so my phone was ringing and um I had
it face down and one of my friends was
like, "Somebody calling your phone." And
I thought it was a joke. And then I
answered the phone and I heard uh the
gym talking and you know it was just
emotional just to uh see you know me uh
get drafted. You know I'm from Yu City.
It's a small town and you know uh not a
lot of people come out of there. So for
me to be one of the guys that you know
came out of is it's a special it was
special moment for me.
>> Yeah that's great to hear. I also you
talked about your route running and the
the way you felt you you know produced
in that area. I was reading about you
that your drop number increased every
year at Louisville. your route tree
increased there. How would you describe
your growth and your improvement during
your time there at Louisville?
>> Uh I would say uh I feel like it was it
was it was pretty good just to uh just
to be at Louisville for four years and
you know keep growing you know as a
player and as a person. Uh I know it
took a lot for me to you know become the
person I am and the player I am but you
know um those Louisville coaches and the
staff you know really uh you know shaped
me into who I am. So yeah.
>> Isaiah
going on, Chris. Uh, I echo everyone's
congratulations and welcome to the city,
man. Thank you.
>> Um, I wanted to ask about something you
just mentioned. You said that obviously
you stayed at Louisville for four years.
Obviously, that's rare in today's
college football world. I'm curious what
led to you staying there for all four
years. Uh, I would just say, uh, Pete
Noctton. He's a recruiting coordinator
on he was a recruiting coordinator on
the staff when u I came in and uh he
just, you know, told me that he was
going to take me under his wing. He's
going to take care of me and uh I'm I'm
going to have a great season. I mean, a
great uh, you know, career at
Louisville. He told me I'll be in his
position today. So, I took that, you
know, uh, when I was in high school and
I said, I feel like I could trust this
guy. So, um, and everything that he said
was true, you know, and I just felt like
Louisville kind of, you know, knew knew
knew me as a player and knew how to make
me better and and as you can see, you
know, I got better each and every year.
And, um, those guys just, you know,
shape me into who I am. You know, I feel
like, you know, they shaped me into a
man.
>> That's what's up. That's what's up. Uh,
the Dolphins have a big need at
receiver. I know you're excited just to
be drafted um regardless of where it
would be, but kind of talk to me a
little bit about the opportunity to be
able to contribute um almost from day
one or whenever you get healthy.
>> Man, it's a blessing, man. It's a
blessing, bro. Just to just to be in
this in this position is a blessing,
man. That's all I can say.
>> Cool. Appreciate you, man.
>> Thank you,
>> Kyle.
>> Hey, Chris. Congratulations, man.
>> Thank you. I wanted to ask you about uh
your wide receivers's coach Dion Branch.
Obviously a guy had a lot of success in
the league and I was curious what some
of the things were that maybe you
learned from him about chopping it up
about playing wide receiver.
>> Uh I would say uh what I learned is
first off just how to be a pro, you
know, and how to carry myself, you know,
on and off the field. Um you know, I
feel like he played a big part of me,
you know, growing into this mature
person that I am now. Uh it was just the
things he said I had the on the field
things. It was just a thing things that
you know I could uh you know be better
at like building a routine or you know
my eating habits and things like that
when I was at Louisville and I was I
learned so much you know you know I put
so much in my game just off having him
for one season. It it made my game
elevate so much more. So u it was a
blessing to have Dion Branch and when I
found out he was going to be my coach my
senior year that's all I need to know to
stay. How how different was that
relationship when he was director of
player development versus when he came
over and coached you for wide receivers?
>> Yeah, so Dion always been like a on on
the um coaching st on the uh staff, but
uh it was just uh more of so you know we
could you know connect more and we spent
more time and stuff like that together.
So he we always had that uncle and um
nephew relationship, but uh it's just
that when he became my position coach,
you know, we we we spent more time
together.
>> Appreciate it.
Hal.
>> Hi, Chris. Welcome to South Florida.
>> Thank you.
>> Um, I wanted to ask you about your big
day against Miami here at Hard Rock
Stadium. What was clicking for you that
day? And how much of a factor do you
think it was in the Dolphins drafting
you? Did they bring it up uh in their
discussions with you?
>> Um, yeah. They uh talked about the uh
Miami game when I was at the uh at the
combine. But uh what was clicking for me
uh you know they was number two, you
know, in the uh in college football
around the time. You know, I feel like,
you know, this just uh something that I
like to, you know, I like to go up
against. You know, when we, you know, we
we was ranked low and um I just wanted
to prove everybody that I am who I say I
am. And um I just wanted to shock, you
know, shock the world and and that's
what we did as a team. Uh, I just felt
like, you know, when I had my guys
behind me and, uh, things like that, you
know, that was clicking. So, yeah.
>> Oh, thank you,
>> Isaiah.
>> Just one more for me, Isaiah Smalls,
Miami Herald. Uh, you talked about, you
know, being a receiver that kind of
feels like he was overlooked in the
process because of, you know, obviously
the injury, right? Um, I know Almanra, I
believe, has like the list of receivers
taken before him. I I don't I'm curious,
are you gonna go to that extreme, but
just like how do you plan to, I guess,
stay motivated knowing that like you
probably should have been drafted
higher?
>> Because I know uh I've been having, you
know, this uh this ranking on um on
front of my home screen since uh this
this this pre-draft started. Uh, I know,
you know, and it's it's going to be in
my mind, you know, I'm going to write
that on my mirror and every day I wake
up, I'm going to see I'm I'mma tell
myself this how many guys they took
before you, you know, this this this how
long it took you, you know, to get
drafted. So, I'm I'm I'm going to show
everybody and I'm going prove everybody,
you know, like I said, I am who I say I
am.
>> You you said you have what on your home
screen?
>> Uh, it's it's like a college ranking of
all the receivers. You know, I'm kind of
at the bottom of the list. I feel like,
you know, that's my motivation every
day. I wake up in the morning.